http://www.marketresearch.org.uk/privacy_policy

Research Jobfinder
The No.1 jobs resource for research	and insight professionals
Research Buyer's Guide (RBG)
The only source of accredited research suppliers in the UK and Ireland
Research Live
The definitive source of research news and opinion
International Journal of Market Research (IJMR)
The world authority on research methodologies and techniques
Fair Data
The Fair Data mark helps consumers recognise who they can trust
Geodemographics (GKB)
For people interested in the application of geodemographics and big data
Research for small businesses
Tips and case studies for how SMEs can use research to grow their business.
Recruiter Accreditation
The RAS website provides training materials for use by qualitative research recruiters.
Settings
Update your password, personal details and email preferences.
Services
Access member services and content.
Membership
Membership
We offer a wide range of events to drive innovation, host debate, recognise through awards and connect you with other research professionals.
Company Partner
Company Partner Accreditation demonstrates your organisation's commitment to quality insight while keeping your business compliant, upskilled and competitive.
Become a Company Partner
Why get accredited?
How to get accredited
Benefits - what they are
Benefits - how to login
MRS consultancy
International Affiliate
Networks
Access
Operations Network
&more
Our Company Partners
Company Partner Area
DirectoryData Analytics
Data Analytics
For researchers and analysts alike, MRS provides training, content, networking and awards to help you and your teams deliver effective data analytics and business insight.
Resources
ADA package
Awards
Innovation in Data Analytics Award
Training
Online courses
Face to face
Standards
Data protection
Fair Data
Networking
ADA Network
Standards
Standards
MRS champions the highest ethical, commercial and methodological practices in research.We provide fair regulation, clear guidance and practical advice. We help research flourish.
Professional standards
Home
Code of Conduct
Binding Guidelines
MRS Guidance
Quality standards
IQCS
ISO 20252
Research participants
Been contacted by a research agency? (Freephone)
Training/CPD
Training/CPD
MRS offers over 70 training courses, professional qualifications, continuous professional development and mentoring to help research, insight and analytics professionals accelerate their learning and careers. You can track your achievements through our specialist CPD system.
Training
Search training courses
About MRS training
Courses by A-Z
Courses by month
Online courses
Training webinars
In-company training
CPD
What is CPD?
Register
MRS Professional Development Framework
Accredited CPD providers
CPD Information Handbook
Accreditation
Accredited centre area
List of MRS accredited centres
Become an accredited centre
Events
Every year MRS helps 11,000 professionals find inspiration, practical help and profitable new relationships. We are the most active supplier of events and networks for the research world.
Search all events
Search training courses
&more
Speaker evenings
Professional webinars
Awards
Roadshows
Networking events
Conferences
Other events
Call for contributions
Resources
Resources
MRS provides you with the research world's most powerful sources of intelligence. Research and business professionals trust our websites and publications to anticipate and adapt to change, profit from understanding and connect to the market.
Case studies
Archive of market and social research
Awards case studies
Oral history of market research
Video library
Webinar library
Career support
Develop your CV
Impact magazine
International Journal of Market Research (IJMR)
Glossary of terms
Social grade
Research Buyer's Guide
Research industry statistics
Industry size and growth rates
Industry league tables
Search
AwardsNewsAboutContact UsOther MRS sites
Research Job FinderThe Research Buyers Guide (RBG)Research LiveInternational Journal of Market Research (IJMR)Fair DataGeodemographics (GKB)Research for small businesses
Login
Sign In
Sign In
Keep me signed in
Sign In
Forgot username or password?
orCreate account
Close
Gallery
Close
Video
Close
Iframe
Close
Advanced
No results found
Search for...
MRS page
Event
Publications
Training course
Video
Blog post
MRS news
Research Live
Impact Magazine
Clear
All MRS websites use cookies to help us improve our services. Any data collected is anonymised. If you continue using this site without accepting cookies you may experience some performance issues. Read about our cookies here.
Accept and continue
Cookie Settings
UK research sector valued at £7 billion and largest supplier of research and insight in Europe
Home—Privacy and cookies
Privacy and cookies
Useful Links
Join Now
Terms & Conditions
Conference terms & conditions
Membership terms & conditions
Privacy and cookies
Sitemap
Media Centre
How to complain
The Market Research Society respects the privacy of its members and users of its websites. This privacy statement explains the data processing practices of the MRS.
Introduction and General Terms
In this policy “We”, “Us” and “Our” means The Market Research Society incorporated and registered in England and Wales with company number 00518685 and whose registered office is at 15 Northburgh Street, London, EC1V 0JR.
We operate a number of websites and are active on social media platforms, including mrs.org.uk. See below for a full list.
This policy applies to our use of any personal information we collect from you via any of our online services.
It also relates to Our use of any personal information which We obtain from you by phone, email, in letters and other correspondence or in person.
MRS websites
mrs.org.ukfairdata.org.ukinsight.mrs.org.ukmymrs.mrs.org.ukresearch-live.comsmallbusinessresearch.co.uktwitter.com/researchlivetwitter.com/tweetijmrtwitter.com/tweetmrstwitter.com/fairdatafacebook.com/marketresearchsocietylinkedin.com/company/market-research-society-mrs-/facebook.com/marketresearchsociety/
Our commitment to your privacy
MRS takes your privacy very seriously and We are committed to protecting your personal information.  This Privacy and Cookies Policy explains how We collect and use the information you give us. Please read this policy carefully. If you have any questions please contact info@mrs.org.uk
As the founder of the Fair Data accreditation, you can trust that We will manage and treat your personal data with respect.  We will collect, store and manage it in an unbiased and secure way.  We will only use your data for purposes that We have informed you about.  We will always be transparent about the personal data We collect and how We use it.
We will ensure that all personal information supplied is held securely and in accordance with all applicable Data Protection legislation.
Who are we?
MRS is the world's leading research association. We are for everyone with professional equity in market, social and opinion research and in business intelligence, market analysis, customer insight and consultancy. MRS represents both large businesses and SMEs and we have a range of research suppliers included in our membership. We support best practice in the research industry by setting and enforcing industry standards.
What information will we collect from you?
The personal information that We collect from you will vary depending on the context of your interactions with us and the service and/or product that we are providing to you. It may include, but is not limited to, the following information about you:
name;
image and/or voice captured through photography, filming, videotaping and/or audio recording;
demographic data such as your date of birth, gender, educational background; job title; professional memberships; country;
contact data such as email address; home and/or work postal address, postcode; phone number;
payment data such as payment instruments (e.g. credit card numbers) and the associated security code or other financial details(where you make a payment to Us);
information from queries and/or complaints registered with Us;
information about the way you use Our Website, so that We can improve the effectiveness of Our business (see our Cookies Policy for more information);
any other information which may be collected in the course of Our interactions with you.
Please note that sometimes we will require you to provide additional personal information, and sometime sensitive personal information, such as disability and health requirements if this is necessary to provide you with a service or product.
How do we collect information about you?
We collect information about you:
when you register for a web account with Us;
request product or services;
become a member;
participate in promotions;
attend events;
take qualifications;
enter competitions;
provide Us with your personal information from your usage of Our website and any other information you post on Our website, e-mail or otherwise send to Us;
or otherwise provide Us with information in the course of Our interactions with you.
Persons under 16 should not disclose to us any personal information without first getting the permission of a parent or a guardian.
How do we use this information?
We use your personal information:
to enable Us to supply you with the goods and services and information which you have requested;
to analyse the information We collect so that We can administer, support and improve and develop Our business and services We offer;
to predict what you might be interested in;
to provide you with access to certain parts of Our website;
for all other purposes consistent with the proper performance of Our operations and business; and
to contact you for your views on Our products and services.
We may also email you about information or activities that We think you might be interested in. If you do not want us to send you updates like this, please contact us at Market Research Society, 15 Northburgh Street, London EC1V 0JR or by email at info@mrs.org.uk.
What are the legal bases we use for processing your information?
The GDPR requires Us to rely on one or more lawful bases to use your personal information. We consider the bases listed below to be relevant:
Where you have provided your consent for us to use your personal information in a certain way (for example, we will ask for your consent to send you marketing material by email, and we may ask for your explicit consent to collect special categories of your personal information).
Where necessary so that we can comply with a legal obligation to which we are subject (for example, where we are obliged to share your personal information with regulatory bodies which govern our work and services).
Where necessary for the performance of a contract to which you are a party or to take steps at your request prior to entering a contract (for example, to administer your membership or allow you to participate in an event for which you have registered).
Where there is a legitimate interest in us doing so if it is reasonably necessary to achieve our or others’ legitimate interests (as long as that processing is fair, balanced and does not unduly impact your rights).
“Legitimate Interests” means Our interests in conducting and managing our business as the professional body for research, insight and analytics and as the regulator promoting high professional standards throughout the sector.  For example, we have an interest in making sure our marketing is relevant for you, so we may process your information to send you marketing that is tailored to your interests. As we are a professional awarding body we have an interest in making available and publishing successful candidate results such as in print and digital channels of Impact Magazine. We also have an interest in processing your information, to undertake research for MRS or on behalf of third parties, in order to inform our knowledge base and assist our representation of the sector. Our interests also allow us to communicate with you to ensure that you can participate in the governance of the society we will process your information to send you communications about the Annual General Meeting and election notices and to co-operate on charitable activities for the sector through the Market Research Benevolent Association (MRBA) and the Archive of Market and Social Research (AMSR).
It can also apply to processing that is in your interests as well. For example, we may process your information to protect you against fraud when transacting on our website, and to ensure our websites and systems are secure or
When we process your personal information for Our legitimate interests, we make sure to consider and balance any potential impact on you (both positive and negative), and your rights under data protection legislation. Our legitimate interests do not automatically override your interests - we will not use your personal information for activities where our interests are overridden by the impact on you (unless we have your consent or are otherwise required or permitted to by law).
If you have any concerns about Our processing, you have the right to object to processing that is based on our legitimate interests. For more information on your rights, please see Section 12 on “Your Rights” below.
Will we ever share your information?
We may use selected agents to process your information on Our behalf, such as software providers to host Our website.  Such third parties will be authorised to see and use your information but only to fulfil their contractual obligations to Us and will not be permitted to use it for any other purpose.  We retain full responsibility for how your personal information may be used by such agents.
In exceptional circumstances We may share your information when We are legally required to do so.
When requested by you, We may pass on your personal information to third parties who may send you details of goods and services that may be of interest to you.  For example, if you attend an event, your details may be shared with the speakers, trainers and/or sponsors at the event.  If this is of interest to you, please tick the box on the relevant registration form, opting in for such contact.  If at any time you would prefer not to receive this information, please contact Us at Market Research Society, 15 Northburgh Street, London EC1V 0JR or by email at info@mrs.org.uk.
How do we protect your personal information?
We place great importance on the security of your personal information and We always try to take appropriate precautions to protect it. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help Us protect your personal data from unauthorised access, use or disclosure. For example when we transmit highly confidential data (such as a credit card number or password) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption.
Despite all of Our precautions however, no data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.  So, whilst We strive to protect your personal information, We cannot guarantee the security of any information which you send to Us and you must understand that you do so at your own risk.
How long do We keep your personal information for?
The length of time We hold your personal information varies depending upon the type of information and its use.  We will hold your personal information on Our systems only for as long as necessary to provide the services and/or products that you have requested, or for such other essential purposes such as investigating disciplinary matters, complying with  our legal obligations, resolving disputes, and enforcing our agreements.
The actual retention periods for different types of personal information that we hold can be found here  If you have any questions about Our data retention policy, please email: info@mrs.org.uk
Where do we store and process your information?
We generally store and process your information within the European Economic Area (EEA).
Where we need to transfer your information outside of the European Economic Area we only do so to countries which have been determined by the European Commission to have an adequate level of data protection//or where We transfer personal information to countries that have not been determined to have an adequate level of protection we do so using a variety of legal mechanisms, including contracts, to help ensure your rights and protections.
What are your rights?
You have specific rights connected to provision of your personal information to Us. These include your rights to request that We:
confirm to you what personal information we may hold about you, if any, and for what purposes
change the consent which you have provided to us in relation to your personal information
correct any inaccurate or incomplete personal information which we may hold about you
provide you with a complete copy of your personal data for you to move elsewhere
provide you with a complete copy of your personal information for you to move elsewhere where you have provided this information by consent or by a contract with Us
stop the processing of your personal information, whilst an objection from you is being resolved
permanently erase all your personal information promptly, and confirm to you that this has been done(there may be reasons why we may be unable to do this)
stop the processing of your personal information for the purpose of direct marketing
You also have the right to
withdraw consent that you have provided to us to process your personal information, at any time
object to profiling or to any decisions being taken by Us by automated means
If you have a concern about the way we are collecting or using your personal data, if We do not address your request, or fail to provide you with a valid reason why we have been unable to do so, you have the right to contact the Information Commissioner’s Office to make a complaint. They can be contacted via their websitehttps://ico.org.uk/concerns/ or by telephone 0303 123 1113.
How can you access your information and contact Us?
You have the right to access any personal information that you have submitted to Us. We give you the following options for requesting this information from Our database:
Access your account: Sign in at mrs.org.uk and use the “My account' feature to see personal information provided when you registered with us and change privacy settings in your account.
Send Us an email: info@mrs.org.uk. Be sure to include your name and clear instructions on what you would like Us to do.
Write to Us at: 15 Northburgh Street, London, EC1V 0JR. Be sure to include your name and clear instructions on what you require.
If you require Us to supply you with details of the personal information that We hold about you, then we will provide this information free of charge and we will provide this information to you within 30 days of your request unless the request is complex or is numerous requests. If this is the case we will inform you within 30 days of your request about the reason for the extension of time. If your request is manifestly unfounded or excessive we will either charge a reasonable fee or provide an explanation for our refusal to respond.
Changes to your details or this policy
If your personal details change, please help Us to keep your information up to date by notifying Us at the email address at the beginning of this policy.
We may revise or update this policy from time to time to reflect changes in Our activities or for other purposes. If We do so, We will post notice of the change on Our website. Please revisit this policy each time you consider giving personal information.
This privacy policy was last updated 11 October 2018.
About cookies and similar technologies
A “cookie” is a small, often encrypted text file, located in your web browser directory. The text in a cookie often consists of a string of numbers and letters that uniquely identifies your computer, but it can contain other information as well.  Cookies are often used by web pages to help users navigate their websites efficiently and perform certain functions within the page or login.
Similar technologies such as pixel tags (also known as beacons and clear GIFs) are also used to measure the success of email communications.
Each website can send its own cookie to your web browser if your browser preferences allow it. Similar technologies are also often used within emails to understand whether the email had been read and if any links have been clicked.
We use this information to track your movements through Our website, to find out how it is being used and to assess its usefulness. Personal information about you is not collected during the tracking process.
Internet browsers normally accept cookies by default.  However, it is possible to set an internet browser to reject cookies.  By using Our website you are consenting to Our use of cookies unless you set your internet browser to reject cookies.
You can disable the cookies that We attach if your browser supports this. For further information on how to do this, please refer to www.allaboutcookies.org. However, you should bear in mind that if you exercise this option, you may be unable to use some of Our on-line services.
The cookies we use
You can change the cookie settings of our website here.
Below we have described the main cookies and similar technologies We use and what We use them for:
Operationally Necessary. We use cookies, web beacons, or other similar technologies that are necessary to the operation of our sites, services, applications, and tools. This includes technologies that allow you access to our sites, services, applications, and tools; that are required to identify irregular site behaviour, prevent fraudulent activity and improve security; or that allow you to make use of our functions such as shopping-carts, saved search, or similar functions.
Performance. We use cookies, web beacons, or other similar technologies to assess the performance of our websites, applications, services, and tools, including as part of our analytic practices to help us understand how our visitors use our websites, determine if you have interacted with our messaging, determine whether you have viewed an item or link, or to improve our website content, applications, services, or tools; For example we use a tracking mechanism so we can monitor and improve the marketing emails we send you. This involves attaching a piece of code to each marketing email which is sent by MRS.
We also use Google Analytics which are used widely by websites to collect information about how website visitors use a site. We use Google Analytics cookies to collect information about how users use Our website and to improve Our website. Google Analytics collect information in an anonymous form and will not allow Us to identify you or collect any personal information about you.  Google Analytics do not track your internet activity after leaving Our website.
Functionality. We use cookies, web beacons, or other similar technologies that allow us to offer you enhanced functionality when accessing or using our sites, services, applications, or tools. This may include identifying you when you sign into our sites or keeping track of your specified preferences, interests, or past items viewed so that we may enhance the presentation of content on our sites;
Advertising or Targeting.  We use first-party or third-party cookies and web beacons to deliver content, including ads relevant to your interests, on our sites or on third party sites.  This includes using technologies to understand the usefulness to you of the advertisements and content that have been delivered to you, such as whether you have clicked on an advertisement.
Hyperlinks and third party cookiesMRS websites may contain hyperlinks to websites owned and operated by third parties and buttons and content from social media sites such as Facebook, Twitter and YouTube. Social media cookies enable you to share content from Our website with your social media networks
These third parties (including, for example, advertising networks and providers of external services like web traffic analysis services) have their own privacy policies, and may also use cookies,. These cookies are likely to be analytical/performance cookies or targeting cookie. Their policies will govern the use of personal information you submit when visiting these websites, which may also be collected by cookies. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for the privacy practices of such third party websites and your use of such websites is at your own risk.
Individual cookies with description and expiration
The Market Research Society has a network of website which use a variety of cookies. Below is a breakdown of all of the cookies which we use and the domains they are active upon.
Necessary Cookies
Strictly necessary cookies are required to provide you with the best experience when navigating through our website. Without the strictly necessary cookies we cannot provide some functionality necessary for our membership services and navigational redirects.
Cookie
Expires
Description
Domain
SESSID
On browser close
A unique randomly generated string of letter and numbers which is assigned to every user to identify the path and action taken throughout the site. This is used for debugging and maintenance purposes to show problem paths users have found.
mrs.org.uk
www.research-live.com
www.fairdata.org.uk
www.fairdatachecklist.mrs.org.uk
ras.mrs.org.uk
www.mrsannualconference.com
fasttrack.mrs.org.uk
www.researchforsmallbusinesses.com
www.synygissurveys.com
user/cookiepolicyaccepted
1 year
This is the cookie notification popup that appears when entering the site for first time. After selecting "OK" this cookie ensures it doesn’t continue to appear unnecessarily.
mrs.org.uk
www.research-live.com
www.fairdata.org.uk
www.fairdatachecklist.mrs.org.uk
ras.mrs.org.uk
www.mrsannualconference.com
fasttrack.mrs.org.uk
www.researchforsmallbusinesses.com
www.synygissurveys.com
ticker
On browser close
This is the ticker popup that appears when entering the site. After selecting "x" this cookie ensures it doesn't continue to appear unnecessarily.
mrs.org.uk
ras.mrs.org.uk
fasttrack.mrs.org.uk
www.fairdatachecklist.mrs.org.uk
imis_user
1 Month
Stores the users imis information so when the cookie is found, the user does not need to continue to sign up for various parts of the site.
mrs.org.uk
www.research-live.com
redirect_page
On browser close
This stores the currently viewed page so after logging in it will know and redirect you from the page you were previously on.
mrs.org.uk
video_campaign_{number}
1 Month
Stores the users sign up information so when the cookie is found, the user does not need to continue to sign up for campaigns.
mrs.org.uk
ASP.NET_SessionId
On browser close
An anti-request forgery token. Page sent from the server and page responded to by the users browser must have the same token. Helps to prevent request forgery injections. The contents here are encrypted and signed.
mymrs.org.uk
AnonymousCartId
4 days
Standard ASP.NET Session ID – helps iMIS web pages link the actions of a user to the right browser session detail for continuing a user’s session. Helps to ensure continuity of info in SessionState and ViewState. It does not control role, security, or permissions. Deleting or modifying this cookie will not cause the user to be logged out but will force state information to be reloaded
mymrs.org.uk
Asi.Web.Browser.CookiesEnabled
On browser close
Contains role and security info. This cookie is encrypted and encoded. Helps to ensure security at login. These are deleted on Sign Out.
mymrs.org.uk
Login
On browser close
Used to merge a user’s cart when after they login if they already had placed items in their cart while browsing anonymously.
mymrs.org.uk
__RequestVerificationToken
On browser close
Global value to let other iMIS functions know that they can read the cookie values if needed.
mymrs.org.uk
__gads
Various
This cookie is associated with the DoubleClick for Publishers service from Google. Its purpose is to monitor the showing of advertisements on the site, for which the owner may earn some revenue. The main purpose of this cookie is targeting/advertising.
www.research-live.com
Performance Cookies
Performance cookies help us to improve your experience on our website through enhanced functionality. The cookies may be set by us or by third party providers whose services we use. If you do not allow these cookies then some or all of these services may not function properly.
Cookie
Expires
Description
Domain
uid
30 minutes
The cookies are created and read by the AddThis social sharing site, this cookie is private and unique identifier for every user to distinguish the point of share which is used to enhance and monitor the site. For more information about Addthis visit http://www.addthis.com/privacy or to opt out visithttp://www.addthis.com/privacy/opt-out
mrs.org.uk
www.research-live.com
www.fairdata.org.uk
www.mrsannualconference.com
www.researchforsmallbusinesses.com
__atuvc/__atuvs
2 years
The cookies are created and read by the AddThis social sharing site JavaScript on the client side in order to make sure the user sees the updated count if they share a page and return to it before our share count cache is updated. No data from that cookie is sent back to AddThis and removing it when disabling cookies would cause unexpected behaviour for users. For more information about Addthis visit http://www.addthis.com/privacy or to opt out visithttp://www.addthis.com/privacy/opt-out
mrs.org.uk
www.research-live.com
www.fairdata.org.uk
www.mrsannualconference.com
www.researchforsmallbusinesses.com
Analytical Cookies
Analytical cookies help us to know which pages are the most and least popular and see how visitors move around the website. These are non-essential cookies that the used to better our platform. If you do not allow these cookies we will not know when you have visited our site, and will not be able to monitor its performance. All analytical data is collected anonymously.
Cookie
Expires
Description
Domain
_utma
2 years from set/update
Used to distinguish users and sessions. The cookie is created when the javascript library executes and no existing __utma cookies exists. The cookie is updated every time data is sent to Google Analytics.
mrs.org.uk
www.research-live.com
www.fairdata.org.uk
www.fairdatachecklist.mrs.org.uk
ras.mrs.org.uk
www.mrsannualconference.com
fasttrack.mrs.org.uk
www.researchforsmallbusinesses.com
__utmt
10 minutes
Used to throttle request rate.
mrs.org.uk
www.research-live.com
www.fairdata.org.uk
www.fairdatachecklist.mrs.org.uk
ras.mrs.org.uk
www.mrsannualconference.com
fasttrack.mrs.org.uk
www.researchforsmallbusinesses.com
__utmb
30 mins from set/update
Used to determine new sessions/visits. The cookie is created when the javascript library executes and no existing __utmb cookies exists. The cookie is updated every time data is sent to Google Analytics.
mrs.org.uk
www.research-live.com
www.fairdata.org.uk
www.fairdatachecklist.mrs.org.uk
ras.mrs.org.uk
www.mrsannualconference.com
fasttrack.mrs.org.uk
www.researchforsmallbusinesses.com
__utmc
End of browser session
Not used in ga.js. Set for interoperability with urchin.js. Historically, this cookie operated in conjunction with the __utmb cookie to determine whether the user was in a new session/visit.
mrs.org.uk
www.research-live.com
www.fairdata.org.uk
www.fairdatachecklist.mrs.org.uk
ras.mrs.org.uk
www.mrsannualconference.com
fasttrack.mrs.org.uk
www.researchforsmallbusinesses.com
__utmz
6 months from set/update
Stores the traffic source or campaign that explains how the user reached your site. The cookie is created when the javascript library executes and is updated every time data is sent to Google Analytics.
mrs.org.uk
www.research-live.com
www.fairdata.org.uk
www.fairdatachecklist.mrs.org.uk
ras.mrs.org.uk
www.mrsannualconference.com
fasttrack.mrs.org.uk
www.researchforsmallbusinesses.com
__utmv
2 years from set/update
Used to store visitor-level custom variable data. This cookie is created when a developer uses the _setCustomVar method with a visitor level custom variable. This cookie was also used for the deprecated _setVar method. The cookie is updated every time data is sent to Google Analytics.
mrs.org.uk
www.research-live.com
www.fairdata.org.uk
www.fairdatachecklist.mrs.org.uk
ras.mrs.org.uk
www.mrsannualconference.com
fasttrack.mrs.org.uk
www.researchforsmallbusinesses.com
_ga
2 years
This cookie is a randomly generated number which is used as a client identifier on Google Analytics. It is included in each page request in a site and used to calculate visitor, session and campaign data for the sites analytics reports.
mrs.org.uk
www.research-live.com
www.fairdata.org.uk
www.fairdatachecklist.mrs.org.uk
ras.mrs.org.uk
www.mrsannualconference.com
fasttrack.mrs.org.uk
www.researchforsmallbusinesses.com
_gat
10 Minutes
This cookie is used to throttle the request rate - limiting the collection of data on high traffic websites.
mrs.org.uk
www.research-live.com
www.fairdata.org.uk
www.fairdatachecklist.mrs.org.uk
ras.mrs.org.uk
www.mrsannualconference.com
fasttrack.mrs.org.uk
www.researchforsmallbusinesses.com
_gid
24 Hours
This cookie is a randomly generated number which is used as a client identifier on Google Analytics. It is included in each page request in a site and used to calculate visitor, session and campaign data for the sites analytics reports.
mrs.org.uk
www.research-live.com
www.fairdata.org.uk
www.fairdatachecklist.mrs.org.uk
ras.mrs.org.uk
www.mrsannualconference.com
fasttrack.mrs.org.uk
www.researchforsmallbusinesses.com
Get the latest MRS news
Our newsletters cover the latest MRS events, policy updates and research news.
Sign up
The Research Buyers Guide
Find your next agency
Powered by the Research Buyers Guide
Advanced Search
Companies
Facilities
Search
Worldwide
---Select an entry---AfricaAustralasiaCanadaCaribbeanCentral AmericaCentral AsiaCentral EuropeChinaEastern EuropeFranceIndia/PakistanJapanMiddle EastNorthern/Western EuropeOtherPacific RimRepublic of IrelandRussiaScandinaviaSouth AmericaUKUSAWorldwide
Services 0
Clear
Access Panels
Advanced data
Advanced Statistical Techniques
Audience Measurement
Benchmark Studies
Biometrics
Web Usability Research
---Select an entry---Access PanelsAdvanced dataAdvanced Statistical TechniquesAudience MeasurementBenchmark StudiesBiometricsBrainstormingCAI ProgrammersCAPICATICo-creationCoding/Data EntryConsultancyContinuousCopy TestingCreative development researchCustomData MiningDeliberative ResearchDepth InterviewsDesk ResearchDiary StudiesDiscourse analysisEthnographyEvent EvaluationExecutive/Industrial InterviewsEye TrackingFace-to-FaceForeign LanguagesGamificationGeo-demographic modellingGroup Discussions/Focus GroupsHall TestsIn-Home/Doorstep InterviewsIn-Store InterviewsInternet Research/CAWIKiosk InterviewsLiterature reviewsMarket reviews and analysismCAPIMobile Web SurveysMultivariate Stats and ModellingMystery ShoppingNeuromarketingObservationOmnibus SurveysOnline CommunitiesOnline Focus Group HostingOnline Results and Data PortalsOnline SurveysPanelsPostal ResearchQualitativeQuantitativeQuestionnaire DesignRapid evidence assessmentsRecruitingReport WritingRetail AuditsScript WritersSemioticsSMSSocial/CGM MonitoringStreet/Mall InterviewsSyndicated SurveysTabulation & AnalysisTelephone InterviewingTrackingTranscriptionViewing FacilitiesVolumetricsWeb Usability Research
Expertise 0
Clear
Advertising
Analytics
Behavioural Analysis
Behavioural Change
Brand/Branding
Business-to-Business
Web Analytics
---Select an entry---AdvertisingAnalyticsBehavioural AnalysisBehavioural ChangeBrand/BrandingBusiness-to-BusinessClinical TrialsCommunications/PRCompetitive IntelligenceConcept TestingConsumerCrowdsourcingCustomer CommunitiesCustomer LoyaltyCustomer SatisfactionData AnalyticsData FusionDirect Marketing/PromotionsE-CommerceEmerging MarketsEmployee ResearchForecastingInternationalMedia MonitoringMulti-Mode FieldworkNew Product DevelopmentOnline PanelsOpinion PollingPackaging/DesignPricingProduct TestingReputation ManagementSimulated Test MarketsSocial MediaSocial NetworkingSocial ResearchTranslationTrendspottingUsage & AttitudeWeb 2.0 ResearchWeb Analytics
Sectors 0
Clear
Accountancy
Agriculture
Automotive
Catering/Hospitality
Charities/Voluntary
Chemicals
Computers – hardware
Computers – software
Drinks (Alcoholic)
Drinks (Non-alcoholic)
Durables/White goods
Education/Training
Electrical Goods
Energy
Engineering
Entertainment – in home
Entertainment – out of home
Environmental
Legal
Media (Broadcast)
Media (Mobile)
Media (Print)
Non-Profit
Nutrition
Office Equipment
Online
Pets/Petcare
Pharmaceutical
Politics
Property/Construction/Housing
Wellness/Fitness
---Select an entry---AccountancyAgricultureAutomotiveCatering/HospitalityCharities/VoluntaryChemicalsComputers – hardwareComputers – softwareDrinks (Alcoholic)Drinks (Non-alcoholic)Durables/White goodsEducation/TrainingElectrical GoodsEnergyEngineeringEntertainment – in homeEntertainment – out of homeEnvironmentalEvents/ConferencesFashion/ClothingFinance/Investment – BusinessFinance/Investment – PersonalFMCG – GeneralFoodGambling/Online GamingGovernment/Local AuthorityHealthcareHome EntertainmentHome/Garden/DIYIndustrialInformation TechnologyInsuranceInteractive EntertainmentInternet/New MediaLegalMedia (Broadcast)Media (Mobile)Media (Print)Non-ProfitNutritionOffice EquipmentOnlinePets/PetcarePharmaceuticalPoliticsProperty/Construction/HousingPublic Services/UtilitiesRetailSMESocial MediaSponsorshipSport/Leisure/ArtsTelecommunicationsTobaccoToiletries/Beauty ProductsToys/GamesTransportationTravel/TourismWellness/Fitness
Respondent types 0
Clear
Affluent
Anti-social/deviant behaviour
Baby Boomers
Bangladeshi
Black African
Black Caribbean
Youth/Teens
---Select an entry---AffluentAnti-social/deviant behaviourBaby BoomersBangladeshiBlack AfricanBlack CaribbeanChineseCollege/University StudentsDigital ConsumersDisabled PeopleEastern EuropeanEthnic MinoritiesGay/Lesbian/Bisexual/TransgenderGender NeutralHard-to-ReachHigh Net WorthHispanic MarketsIndianKidsMature/MidlifeMenMothers/ParentsOffenders/ex-offendersPakistaniSenior CitizensSingle ParentsUnemployedVictims of crimeWelsh speakersWomenYouth/Teens
©2020 The Market Research Society,
15 Northburgh Street, London EC1V 0JR
Tel: +44 (0)20 7490 4911 Email: info@mrs.org.uk
The Market Research Society (MRS) is the world's leading research association. For all those who need, generate or interpret the evidence for making good business and policy decisions. Click here to find out more about us.
Join now
Advertise with us
Terms & conditions
Privacy and cookies
Sitemap
Environmental policy
How to complain
Contact us
©2020 The Market Research Society,
15 Northburgh Street, London EC1V 0JR
Tel: +44 (0)20 7490 4911 Email: info@mrs.org.uk
